<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>architecture on Saúl Zalimben</title><link>https://zalimben.github.io/tags/architecture/</link><description>Recent content in architecture on Saúl Zalimben</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zalimben.github.io/tags/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Software Architect</title><link>https://zalimben.github.io/blog/english/posts/software-architect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zalimben.github.io/blog/english/posts/software-architect/</guid><description>Software Architect is an expert developer who design software solutions from the ground up, making high-level decisions about each stage of the process including technical standards, tools, design principles, platforms to be used, etc., leading a team of engineers to create the final product.
A software architect makes high-level design choices and frames technical standards. This might include tools, software coding standards, or platforms to be used. To be effective, a software architect needs broad (and deep) technical knowledge to make good decisions.</description></item><item><title>Software Architecture</title><link>https://zalimben.github.io/blog/english/posts/software-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zalimben.github.io/blog/english/posts/software-architecture/</guid><description>Architecture is about the important stuff… whatever that is. &amp;ndash;Ralph Johnson
In this rapidly evolving digital landscape, where innovation and efficiency reign supreme, the role of software architecture has become more critical than ever. Fundamentally, software architecture acts as a blueprint for the organization, operation, and communication of software parts. This ensures the robustness, scalability, and upgradability of the system.
A capable software architect creates a solid and elegant software solution that tackles complicated problems and meets user needs, much as a talented architect creates an impressive skyscraper.</description></item></channel></rss>